Jasmine Hung

MANUFACTURING ENGINEER, PROJECT MANAGER, PROCESS EXCELLENCE

Conshohocken, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Jasmine-Hung/ed04546ed3874c89

Experienced, high-energy, results oriented management professional with a strong record of achievement in manufacturing management in the chemical and pharmaceutical industries. Extensive background in batch & continuous processing and specialty polymers & chemicals manufacturing.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SENIOR ENGINEER

HYDE ENGINEERING & CONSULTING - Fort Washington, PA - 2013 to 2014

- •Generated Cleaning Development Protocols for McNeil's Cleaning Validation Initiative and Fort Washington Facility Start-up Certification as mandated per FDA Consent Decree
- Collaborated with Quality and 3rd Party Quantic Reviewers to perform comment resolution in a timely manner
- Incorporated process excellence tools (PFDs and Schematics) to promote Right First Time execution.
- Supported Visible Residue Limits Protocol to establish VRL for Visual Inspection.

SENIOR ENGINEER & PROJECT MANAGEMENT SPECIALIST

MERCK & co., Inc. [West Point Technical Operations - Varicella/ Zostavax (Chickenpox and Shingles Vaccine)] - West Point, PA - 2012 to 2013

- •Managed and Supported SPHERE B62 Facility Expansion to double the manufacturing capacity of stock seed, cell banks and working seed for downstream manufacturing in Durham, West Point and various other sites.
- •Authored Change Control and led implementation of a new Media Suite in B62 to allow for increased raw material to be stored, thawed, warmed, prepped and filtered at the point of use.
- •Implemented -80°C Stirling Portable Shuttles to transfer Stock Seed, Cell Banks and Bulk Vials to the designated cryofreezers to prevent yield loss. Received Peer Recognitions for Right First Time and Sense of Urgency.

STAFF ENGINEER

MERCK & co., Inc. [West Point Technical Operations - VAQTA® Hepatitis A Vaccine] - West Point, PA - 2009 to 2012

- Provided technical support for downstream manufacturing, reduced process deviations, supported Regulatory filings and inspections, developed and implemented process improvements
- •Led Sterile Liquid Filtration Initiative to implement Bioburden Sampling and Gamma Irradiated Redundant Filters
- Authored Variance to reduce Bulk sample volume, increasing supply by 270,000 doses/yr.
- •Led annual Process Simulations and implementation of 100% Soybean Casein Digest Media.
- •Led implementation of new Antigen Assay (EIA 778) to increase robustness and reduce sample volume
- •Supported Implementation of PIP, increasing capacity of facility from 5MM to 10MM doses/yr
- •Managed Process Monitoring Database: supervised Data Contractor, facilitated quarterly and Annual Product Reviews for process shifts/trends. Supported MII Implementation for Cpk Analysis.
- •Mentored Green Belt Candidate in Optimization of VAQTA® Purification Process
- Led 2009 pH Excursion Investigation allowing for release of 10 VAQTA lots to U.S. Pediatric Supply.

OROS FIRST LINE PRODUCTION SUPERVISOR

JOHNSON & JOHNSON, GPSG/ALZA - Vacaville, CA - 2008 to 2009

- •Led Production Team in Granulation Unit Operation to achieve cycle time for daily production demands.
- •Managed employees' performance and development. Trained and certified technicians on various manufacturing operations, documentations, Regulatory requirements and Standard of Work.
- Performed routine troubleshooting, equipment repairs and Compliance/ S&E Audits for production areas.
- •Routinely audited production area to ensure ISO regulations, and Safety and Environmental compliance.
- Conducted Nonconformance investigations, responded to audit observations, and implemented CAPAs.

GTS REMICADE US Bulk (GLOBAL TECHNICAL SUPPORT)

JOHNSON & JOHNSON Global Biologics Supply Chain (GBSC)/ Centecor - Malvern, PA - 2007 to 2008

- •Led extension of Resin Expiry time from 50 to 75 cycles, estimated cost savings of \$948,967(Remicade lifecycle)
- •Led implementation of additional DPC Freeze/Thaw Cycle at Malvern, GSK, Leiden, & St. Louis sites.
- •Supported Low Yield Investigation of Remicade; performed manufacturing troubleshooting, step yield analysis, and corrective implementation of new filters.

SUPPLIER QUALITY ENGINEER

JOHNSON & JOHNSON: ADVANCED STERILIZATION PRODUCTS (ASP) - Irvine, CA - 2007 to 2007

- Six Sigma Green Belt Certification: Developed Preventative Maintenance Program for STERRAD Tools
- •Certified Quality Auditor: Led and supported Quality System Audits for Ext. Mfg suppliers and FDA Audits.
- •Led validation and implementation of SCAR (Supplier Corrective Action Report) database for production use. Reduced backlog of open SCARs by 80% in 2007.
- Developed Phase II of Supplier Scorecard for Supply Chain & Quality Department.

OROS PROCESS ENGINEER

JOHNSON & JOHNSON: GPSG/ALZA - Vacaville, CA - 2006 to 2007

- •Drove projects to improve processes, raw material qualifications, and cost saving initiatives.
- •Led development and validation of Noramco manufactured API for OROS Hydromorphone base dosages.
- Supported qualification and validation of OROS Hydromorphone 4mg extension.
- Completed Performance Qualification of new Polyox material for all OROS product lines.
- •Received Encore Awards for Strategic Thinking, Customer Focus and Sense of Urgency.

EDUCATION

MBA in Statistics for Business and Economics

Lehigh University Bethlehem - Bethlehem, PA March 2012

Bachelor of Science: in Double Major in Chemical Engineering and Biomedical Engineering

Carnegie Mellon University - Pittsburgh, PA 2002 to 2006

SKILLS

Certifications: • Six Sigma Green Belt, Certified Quality Auditor, Global Operations Leadership Development Program Graduate Mfg Applications: • Trackwise, SAP, Portfolio Management, Maximo, One Source/Our Source, Compliance Wire, E-Rthymn, Automagic, E-Ship, Tracksys, KRONOS, MFG-PRO, LIMs, Laboratory: • Quantitative Analysis, packed beds, binary diffusion, Alum Characterization Studies Computer: • JMP,

Minitab, MathCAD, GAUSSIAN, MS Office/Excel/ Access/ Visio, JAVA, LABVIEW, GAMS, SimuLink, Aspen PLUS, MATLAB, Unix, HYSYS 3.4, Chime

LINKS

http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=64480869&trk=nav_responsive_tab_profile

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

My work experience in the Pharmaceutical and Biologics Industry has allowed me to become a Subject Matter Expert as well as a group leader in functional teams. I have also had the opportunity to graduate from the Global Operations Leadership Development Program (GOLD) sponsored by Johnson & Johnson. This program consisted of various roles and responsibilities in Quality, Engineering and Operations within the Biologics, Pharmaceuticals and Medical Device Sectors.

I am highly interested in Technical Operations, Process Excellence and Project Management positions.